Guide to the Records of the Office of External Affairs, Commencement and Special Events RG.7.4
New York University Archives
- Series III: Commencement, 1834-2024; 31.5 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 47 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 52 boxes without container profiles.; 6 audiocassettes; 15.6 Megabytes in 13 computer files
  - Instructions -- Students Procession Marshals, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Instruction for Marshals -- Entrance, Guest Seating, Live TV, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Tickets and Passes, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - NYU Today Issue re: Commencement, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Program, Address, Ephemera, Instructions, Planning Correspondence, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 1-5)
  - Program, Address, Ephemera, Scripts, Instructions, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 6-8, Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Program, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Stage Manager's Park Script, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Instructions for Faculty Procession Marshals, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Instructions for Students Procession Marshals, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Instructions for Marshals -- Entrance, Guest Seating, Live TV, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Tickets, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Script (Annotated), 1994 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Commencement Directory, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Requisitions, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Notices, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Script Synopsis, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Script -- Snow Room (Rain), 1994 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Stage Manager's Abbreviated Park Script (Rain), 1994 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Abbreviated Park Script (Rain), 1994 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Instructions Mailing, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Mailing, Order Forms, Planning Files, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 30-32)
  - Script -- President L. Jay Oliva, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Script with Cues, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Drizzle Script (Annotated), 1994 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Memos, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Catering, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Set-up, Maps, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Staff, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Trustees Dinner, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Program, Planning Files, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 41-42)
  - Valedictory Speech -- Momplaisir, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Script, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Stage Manager's Park Script, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Script - President L. Jay Oliva, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Abbreviated Park Script (Drizzle), 1995 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Snow Script and Set-Up (Rain), 1995 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Memos, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Catering, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Set-up, Maps, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Staff, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Trustee Dinner, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Instructions to Marshals, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Commencement Directory, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Program, Address, Ephemera, Scripts, Instructions, 1995 (Box 83, Folder 2-6)
  - Program, Ephemera, Addresses, Scripts, Instructions, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 7-8, Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Program, Ephemera, Addresses, Scripts, Instructions, Grad Alley Ephemera, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 3-8)
  - Program, Ephemera, Scripts, Instructions, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 9-10, Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Program, Ephemera, Scripts, Instructions, 1999 (Box 85, Folder 3-6, Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Program, Ephemera, Scripts, Instructions, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 2-8)
  - Program, Ephemera, Scripts, Instructions, 2001 (Box 86, Folder 9-10, Box 87, Folder 1-3)
  - Commencement and Baccalaureate Programs, Ephemera, Scripts, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 4-8, Box 88, Folder 1-2)
  - School of Social Work -- Commencement Program, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Steinhardt School of Education -- Commencement Events Programs, 2002-2010 (Box 97, Folder 1-8)
  - Program, Ephemera, Scripts, Instructions, Grad Alley Ephemera, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 3-8)
  - Program, Ephemera, Scripts, Instructions, 2004 (Box 88, Folder 9-10, Box 89, Folder 1-4)
  - Program, Ephemera, Scripts, Instructions, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 5-8)
  - Program, Ephemera, Scripts, Instructions, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 1-7)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science -- Convocation Tickets and Program, 2006, 2009 (Box 96, Folder 17-18)
  - Program, Events Invitations, Scripts, Instructions, 2007 (Box 90, Folder 8-10, Box 91, Folder 1-3)
  - Tiffany ink pen with silver torch, 2007
    ID Number: 433. Description: Tiffany ink pen with silver torch. Creator/Donor/Subject: Office of Commencement and Special Events (RG 7.4).
  - Program, Events Invitations, Ephemera, Scripts, Instructions, 2008 (Box 91, Folder 4-7)
  - Program, Events Invitations, Ephemera, Scripts, Instructions, 2009 (Box 91, Folder 8, Box 92, Folder 1-4)
  - Program, Ephemera, Scripts, Instructions, Grad Alley Ephemera, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 5-7, Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Program, 2011 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Program, Postcard, 2012 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Program, 2013 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Tickets, Schedules, Instructions for Marshals, Scripts, and Grad Alley Material, 2013 (Box Shared University Archives 051, Folder 8-10)
  - Commencement and Grad Alley Programs, Scripts, Tickets, Badges, Hats, and Mailings, 2016 (Box 43, Folder 5-8)
  - Program, 2016 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Commencement and Grad Alley Programs, Invitations, and Mailings, 2018 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Academic Attire Pick-Up Cards, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Bag Check Card and Ticket, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Baseball Cap, 2019 (Box 116)
  - Dinners and Receptions, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Grad Alley, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Greeter Handbook, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, Program, Scripts, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 6-8)
  - Silver Professorships, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Staff Badge, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Tickets and Insert Cards, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 12-13)
  - Yankee Stadium Map, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - All-University Commencement -- Ephemera and Program, 2024
    - Program, Tassel, Ephemera, 2024 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Digital Tickets, UA_RG_7_4_ER_3
  - All-University Commencement -- Greeter Instruction Book, 2024 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - All-University Commencement -- Invitations, 2024; UA_RG_7_4_ER_1
  - All-University Commencement -- Scripts, 2024
    - Paper Scripts (Box 117, Folder 3-4)
    - Electronic Records, UA_RG_7_4_ER_2
  - All-University Commencement -- Training Powerpoint Presentation, UA_RG_7_4_ER_4
  - Grad Alley -- Ephemera, 2024 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - All-University Commencement -- Ephemera and Program, May 15, 2025; cuid19042
    - Program, Tassel, Ephemera (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Digital Tickets, UA_RG_7_4_ER_5
  - All-University Commencement -- Greeter Instruction Book, May 15, 2025 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - All-University Commencement -- Invitations, April-May 2025; UA_RG_7_4_ER_8
  - All-University Commencement -- Scripts, May 15, 2025; cuid19043
    - Paper Scripts (Box 118, Folder 3-4)
    - Electronic Records, UA_RG_7_4_ER_7
  - Grad Alley -- Ephemera, 2025 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Grad Alley -- Production Crew Training Packet, May 2025; UA_RG_7_4_ER_6
  - Programs, Invitations, Notes, undated (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration (GPA) -- Original GPA Banner, undated (Box 100)
- Series IV. Commencement Prizes and Awards, 1941-2000; .50 Linear Feet in one manuscript box.
  This series includes files related to the creation, administration, and distribution of commencement prizes and awards given to staff and graduating students dating from 1941 to 2000. Files in this series typically contain correspondence, check request forms, and notes. Prizes and award titles include the Albert S. Borgman Memorial Prize Fund, Distler-Blankfort Award in Forensics, Distinguished Administrator Award, Distinguished Teaching Medal, and Wortis Biological Prize Fund.
  This series begins with general correspondence, followed by alphabetically arranged files.
  - General Correspondence, 1956, 1971-1974 (Box 95, Folder 1-2)
  - Albert S. Borgman Memorial Prize Fund, 1971, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Alexander L. Shluger Class of 1914 Award, 1955-1973 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Allen Memorial Library Fund, 1952, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Award for Achievement in Dramatics, 1954-1955 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - American Institute of Chemists Medal, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Arthur E. Hill Prize in Chemistry, 1971, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Ben Davidson Memorial Award, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Charles H. Willey Prize Fund, 1971, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Dean Archibald L. Bouton Memorial Fund for Research in English, 1953 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Dean's Undesignated Fund, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Distinguished Administrator Award, 1999 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Distinguished Teaching Medal, 1999-2000 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Distler-Blankfort Award in Forensics, 1941, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Earnest Student Vocal Interpretation of Literature, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Elaine R. Brody Fund, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Frederick Seward Gibson Prize, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Frank N. Morgenstern Award in Social Science, 1966-1973 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - George Augustus Sandham Oration Prize Fund, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - George Schwartz Prize in Biology, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Green Room Best Dramatic Performance Award, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Harold Seidenstein Award, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - The Heights College Alumni Association Award, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Helen M. Jones Prize, 1967-1973 (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Henry Brennecke Prize in German Honors Fund, 1964-1971 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Horace W. Stunkard Prize Fund, 1971, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Isaac and Sophie Sackler Memorial Scholarship, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - James Gordon Bennett Prize, 1971, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - Josiah Marshall Favill Prize Fund, 1957, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - Jerome J. Rich Memorial Prize, 1952-1971 (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - Joseph Daniel Gettler Award in Chemical Research, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 32)
  - Julius Ochs Adler Award, 1956-1973 (Box 95, Folder 33)
  - Maas Essay Prize Winners, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 34)
  - Minnie Kramer Cowin Prize, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 35)
  - Morton S. Rimer Memorial Award, 1957 (Box 95, Folder 36)
  - Murray Altman Prize, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 37)
  - New York University Alumnae Club Key Pin, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 38)
  - New York University Chemistry Alumni Club Prize, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 39)
  - Novice Debate Award, 1957 (Box 95, Folder 40)
  - Perley Lenwood Thorne Medal, 1969-1973 (Box 95, Folder 41)
  - Phi Sigma Delta Prizes in Public Speaking, undated (Box 95, Folder 42)
  - Psychology Department Award, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 43)
  - Samuel F. B. Morse Medal in Physics, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 44)
  - Sandham Prizes in Public Speaking, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 45)
  - Seth Barkas Prize, 1969-1973 (Box 95, Folder 46)
  - Sherborne Vernon Damerel Memorial Prize Fund, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 47)
  - William H. Inman Fellowship, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 48)
  - Winthrop R. Ranney Prize in Music Fund, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 49)
  - Wortis Biological Prize Fund, 1971, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 50)
- Washington Square Park -- Graduation Canopy and Stage Set Up Design and Architectural Plans, 1981-1988 (Flat-file-folder 10)